Preliminary Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office. Records, 1920s-2005 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office. records 1920s-2005 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office
600 linear feet Extent: 450,000 Items
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. The London Office first opened in 1926, and was JWT's first international office and the first international office of any American advertising agency. Consists primarily of account files, Knowledge Center subject files, books and publications, general office files, and the papers of some executives. Major clients represented include DeBeers; Elida Gibbs; Gallaher Tobacco; Guinness; Kellogg's; Kodak; Kraft; Nestlé; Rowntree; Scott Paper; SmithKline Beecham; Unilever; and Warner-Lambert. Includes photographs and slides; scrapbooks; videocassettes; scripts to commercials; and proof sheets of printed advertisements. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
RL.00723
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is restricted.
Unpublished materials are closed to non-JWT employees for 15 years from the date of creation.
Some materials may require additional processing before they can be made available to researchers.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office. Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as gifts in 1987-2009.
Subject Headings
J. Walter Thompson Company; J. Walter Thompson Company. London Office; De Beers Consolidated Mines; Eastman Kodak Company; Gallaher Tobacco; Guinness (Firm); Kellogg Company; Kraft Foods Company; Nestlé Company; Rowntree (Firm); Scott Paper Company; SmithKline Beecham; Unilever (Firm); Warner-Lambert Company; Advertising -- Great Britain; Advertising agencies -- Great Britain; Advertising agencies -- Great Britain -- History; Advertising executives -- England; Photographs; Proofs (printed matter); Scrapbooks; Scripts (documents); Slides (photographs); Videocassettes; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Related Material
Related materials may be found in other collections of the J. Walter Thompson Company Archives:
Account Files Collection
Iconographic Collection
International Advertisements Collection
Newsletter Collection
Publications Collection
Arnold Grisman Papers
Samuel W. (Samuel William) Meek Papers
Thomas Sutton Papers
Frankfurt Office. Harry Clark Papers
Contents of Collection
- Accession (2008-0270), 1920s-2005 and undated, (449 boxes)
  Consists primarily of account files, Knowledge Center subject files, books and publications, general office files, and the papers of some executives. Major clients represented include DeBeers; Elida Gibbs; Gallaher Tobacco; Guinness; Kellogg's; Kodak; Kraft; Nestlé; Rowntree; Scott Paper; SmithKline Beecham; Unilever; and Warner-Lambert. Includes photographs and slides; scrapbooks; videocassettes; scripts to commercials; and proof sheets of printed advertisements.
  - Account Files
    NOTE: Scott, Bowater Scott, Andrex and Kimberly Clark are related companies. Lever, Unilever and Elida Gibbs are related companies. Rowntree and Nestlé are related companies.
    - General (Box 6)
    - General (Box 99)
    - General (Box 249)
    - General (older stuff) (Box 5A)
    - General (older stuff) (Box 6A)
    - General--Andrew Brown (Box 73)
    - General--Derrick Cawston (Box 155)
    - General--Blaise Douglas (Box 231)
    - General--Peter Huber (Box 41)
    - General--Amanda Jardella (scripts and call sheets) (Box 63)
    - General (commercials, television scripts) 1987 (Box 236)
    - General (including Kellogg's, Warner-Lambert, SmithKlineBeecham) (Box 62)
    - General miscellaneous A/V--mostly commercials (Box 240A)
    - General, mainly medical products (JWT Deltacos) (Box 127)
    - General, mainly medical products (JWT Deltacos) (Box 127A)
    - General, mostly old, including Brown & Polson data books (Box 249)
    - General--Scripts (Box 186)
    - Action Bank, Bacardi, Cook Electric, Electricity Council, Kodak, National Westminster, Oxford MOMA (Japan Festival), Pepsi, Warner-Lambert, General account files (Box 137)
    - Addis (Box 1)
    - Addis (Box 168)
    - Andrex (Box 43)
    - Andrex, Nestlé (Box 118)
    - Andrex/Kimberly Clark, Kraft (Box 30)
    - Barclay's Bank, Elida Gibbs, Esso, Jaguar, Kellogg's, Kraft, Northwest Airlines, Rowntree/Nestle, Scott account files (Box 285)
    - Batchelor's, Elida Gibbs, ITV Association, Kellogg's, Kodak, Kraft, Unilever, Yomo (Box 183A)
    - Bowater Scott (Box 140)
    - British Rail, Philips, Rowntree/Nestle, The Observer (Box 128)
    - British Red Cross Gulf Appeal, National Westminster Bank, Pizza Hut, Royal Hospital, Scott account files (videos) (Box 43)
    - British Red Cross, Aquascutum, DeBeers (Box 349)
    - Brooke Bond Foods, Rowntree/Nestlé account files (Box 288)
    - Budweiser, Unilever (Box 3)
    - Campaign for Electoral Reform (Box 249)
    - Canary Wharf (Box 179)
    - Chesebrough-Pond's (Box 86)
    - Chesebrough-Pond's (Box 86A)
    - DeBeers (Box 42)
    - DeBeers (Box 64)
    - DeBeers (Box 75)
    - DeBeers (Box 349)
    - De Beers, Elida Gibbs, Eurotunnel (JWT France), Findus, H.P. Bulmer (Strongbow), Lever, Rowenta (Box 76)
    - DeBeers--Jonathan Manson (Box 64)
    - De Beers, Kellogg's (Box 92)
    - De Beers, Rowntree/Nestlé market research on beverages (bottled water, soft drinks); consumers in the 1990s (Box 278)
    - Dunhill (Box 54)
    - Electricity Council (Box 14)
    - Electricity Council (Box 16)
    - Electricity Council, Kodak (Box 45)
    - Elida Gibbs (Box 41)
    - Elida Gibbs (Box 92A)
    - Elida Gibbs (Box 181A)
    - Elida Gibbs (Box 158)
    - Elida Gibbs (Box 230)
    - Elida Gibbs (Box 281)
    - Elida Gibbs, Scott (Box 281A)
    - Elida Gibbs (Box 290)
    - Elida Gibbs (Box 337)
    - Elida Gibbs (Box 337A)
    - Elida Gibbs (Box 344)
    - Elida Gibbs, Kodak, Lever (Unilever), Nestlé, Sharp, Royal Mail, Rise & Shine (Box 206)
    - Elida Gibbs (Box 206A)
    - Elida Gibbs, Lloyd's Bank, National Westminster Bank, Unilever (Box 193)
    - Elida Gibbs, Milton Bradley, Nicholas Laboratories (Aspro Clear), Thorn EMI, Unilever account files (Box 41)
    - Elida Gibbs, Unilever (Box 85)
    - Elida Gibbs, Unilever (Box 342)
    - Elida Gibbs, Unilever (Box 342A)
    - Esso account files, 1980s-1990s (Box 109)
    - Esso (Box 164)
    - Esso (Box 237)
    - Findus, Royal Air Force (Box 190)
    - Florsheim Europe account files (Box 36)
    - Florsheim Shoes, Lloyd's Insurance account management 1995 (Box 160)
    - Ford, Jaguar (Box 245)
    - Fuji (Kodak?), Harvey's, Rowntree, Scott (Andrex), Wales Tourist Board, Wispa (Box 99)
    - FX Madd (Diamond), Wilkinson Sword (Box 311)
    - Gallaher (Box 146)
    - Gallaher (Box 350)
    - Gallaher (Old Holborn) (Box 231)
    - Gallaher (Old Holborn) (Box 231A)
    - Gallaher, Rowntree (Box 73)
    - Gallaher, Rowntree (Box 73A)
    - Gallaher (mostly personnel files) (Box 69)
    - Gallaher, NatWest (Box 84)
    - Guinness (artwork) (Box 396)
    - Guinness (artwork) (Box 397)
    - Guinness (artwork) (Box 397A)
    - H.P. Bulmer (Strongbow cider) (Box 62A)
    - H.P. Bulmer (Strongbow cider) (Box 96)
    - H.P. Bulmer (Strongbow cider) (Box 341)
    - H.P. Bulmer (Strongbow) (Box 341A)
    - H.P. Bulmer (Strongbow) (Box 349A)
    - Hunt Wesson (Box 193)
    - ITV Association (Box 16)
    - ITV Association (Box 29)
    - ITV Association (Box 46A)
    - ITV Association (Box 62B)
    - ITV Association (Box 110)
    - ITV Association (Box 149)
    - ITV Association (Box 149A)
    - ITV Association, Kellogg's, Kraft (Box 183)
    - ITV Association, Sky Channel, English Premier League account files (Box 29)
    - ITV Association, Jaguar, Rowntree/Nestle, The Observer, Ranks Hovis McDougal, St. Ivel (Box 46)
    - J&B (See also David Baker Papers), Kraft (Box 287)
    - Johnny Walker, Kellogg's, Kraft (Box 111)
    - Kellogg's (Box 18)
    - Kellogg's (Box 24)
    - Kellogg's (Box 25)
    - Kellogg's (Box 26)
    - Kellogg's (Box 32)
    - Kellogg's (Box 38)
    - Kellogg's (Box 60)
    - Kellogg's (Box 70)
    - Kellogg's (Box 81)
    - Kellogg's (Box 87)
    - Kellogg's (Box 92)
    - Kellogg's (Box 94)
    - Kellogg's (Box 95)
    - Kellogg's (Box 101)
    - Kellogg's (Box 107)
    - Kellogg's (Box 139)
    - Kellogg's (Box 143)
    - Kellogg's (Box 147)
    - Kellogg's (Box 166)
    - Kellogg's (Box 172)
    - Kellogg's (Box 193)
    - Kellogg's (Box 210)
    - Kellogg's (Box 212)
    - Kellogg's (Box 216)
    - Kellogg's (Box 218)
    - Kellogg's (Box 219)
    - Kellogg's (Box 222)
    - Kellogg's (Box 227)
    - Kellogg's (Box 228)
    - Kellogg's (Box 235)
    - Kellogg's (Box 240)
    - Kellogg's (Box 247)
    - Kellogg's (Box 247A)
    - Kellogg's (Box 336)
    - Kellogg's (Box 343)
    - Kellogg's, Andrex, Alton Towers (Box 63)
    - Kellogg's commercials (Box 382A)
    - Kellogg's tapes, various masters, Scott (Box 154)
    - Kellogg's, St. Ives (Box 135)
    - Kellogg's Tony Tiger cels (Box 54)
    - Kellogg's, Mattel, R.J. Reynolds (Winston), Unilever (Box 26)
    - Kellogg's, Kraft, Nestle (Box 98)
    - Kellogg's, miscellaneous account files, new business (Box 49)
    - Kellogg's, Red Cross, Scott (Andrex) (Box 124)
    - Kellogg's, Unilever; publications on research (Box 65)
    - Kellogg's, Unilever; publications on research (Box 65A)
    - Kellogg's, RAF account files (Box 282)
    - Kodak (See also Brian Roberts-Wray papers), Benetton (Box 17)
    - Kodak (Box 18)
    - Kodak (Box 28)
    - Kodak (Box 97)
    - Kodak (Box 112)
    - Kodak (Box 112A)
    - Kodak (Box 293)
    - Kodak, Kraft, Jaguar (Box 293A)
    - Kodak (Box 348)
    - Kodak, 1994-96, includes Olympics & photo CD (Box 322)
    - KPMG, Warner-Lambert (Warner-Wellcome) (Listerine and Zantac) (Box 275A)
    - Kraft (Box 22)
    - Kraft (Box 30)
    - Kraft (Box 31)
    - Kraft (Box 67)
    - Kraft (Box 67A)
    - Kraft (Box 74)
    - Kraft (Box 78)
    - Kraft (Box 91)
    - Kraft (Box 116)
    - Kraft (Box 123)
    - Kraft (Box 123A)
    - Kraft (Box 132)
    - Kraft (Box 187)
    - Kraft, Royal Air Force (Box 188)
    - Kraft (Box 201)
    - Kraft (Box 213)
    - Kraft (Box 222)
    - Kraft (Box 286)
    - Kraft (Box 291)
    - Kraft, Andrex, Esso (Box 145)
    - Kraft, J&B, Wilkinson (Box 287)
    - Kraft Philly cheese artwork (Box 55)
    - Lever (Box 121)
    - Lever (Box 122)
    - Lever, H.P. Bulmer (Strongbow) (Box 33A)
    - Lever, SSAFA (Box 119)
    - Lever, SSAFA (Box 119A)
    - Milton Bradley (Box 41)
    - National Lottery (Box 350A)
    - National Westminster Bank (NatWest) (Box 16)
    - National Westminster Bank (NatWest) (Box 19A)
    - Nuclear Electric, Nestle, Kellogg's, Kraft (Box 285)
    - Omega Watch, Kellogg's; StatPak (computer paper); research on eating habits (Box 101)
    - Perspex (Box 37)
    - Perspex (Box 44)
    - Philip cake bread account files; toys, travel (Box 103)
    - Pizza Hut (Box 33)
    - Poly Travel (Box 103)
    - Pond's (Timotei) (Box 86)
    - Pond's (Timotei) (Box 86A)
    - Ponds, Vaseline 1920s/30s, and Campari & Mackesons 1960s-70s (Box 10)
    - Ponds, Vaseline 1920s/30s, and Campari & Mackesons 1960s-70s (Box 10A)
    - R.J. Reynolds (Winston) (Box 26)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 27)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 37)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 43)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 44)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 66)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 68)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 77)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 80)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 89)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 93)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 98)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 100)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 102)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 117)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 121)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 141)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 145)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé, Esso (Box 164)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 182)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 185)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 194)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 195)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 217)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 217A)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 237)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 278)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 284)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 284A)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 339)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 339A)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé--Andrew Brown? (Box 93)
    - Rowntree/Nestle, BMRB report on mint purchasing patterns (Box 48)
    - Rowntree, Hovis, Jaguar (Box 46)
    - Rowntree, Kellogg's (Box 48)
    - Rowntree, Kellogg's, Kraft (Box 285)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Kit Kat) (Box 117)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé; Thompson Way, Scott (Moist TP information) (Box 118)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé (Nestlé, Polo) (Box 102)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé, and General (Box 175)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé, Superchannel (Box 128A)
    - Rowntree, Kellogg's (Box 108)
    - Rowntree/Nestlé, Unilever, Kellogg's, Dalgetty M. Cavendish (Box 167)
    - Royal Air Force (Box 40)
    - Royal Air Force (Box 82)
    - Royal Air Force (Box 130A)
    - Royal Air Force (Box 171)
    - Royal Air Force (Box 199)
    - Royal Air Force (Box 202)
    - Royal Air Force (Box 215)
    - Royal Air Force (Box 224)
    - Royal Air Force (Box 282)
    - Royal Air Force, Cancer (Box 283)
    - Royal Air Force, Cancer (Box 283A)
    - Royal Air Force, Rowntree, Brooke Bond (Box 288)
    - Scott (Box 12)
    - Scott (Box 118)
    - Scott, Kellogg's (Box 148)
    - Scott (Box 156)
    - Scott (Box 196)
    - Scott (Box 200)
    - Scott (Box 212)
    - Scott (Box 225)
    - Scott (Box 296)
    - Scott--David Faulkner, Kraft (Box 184)
    - Scott, Barclays, Elida Gibb, Jaguar, Esso, Northwest Airline (Box 285A)
    - Scott, Andrex (Box 352)
    - Scott/Kimberley Clark (Andrex) account files (Box 30)
    - Steel Co. of Wales, Taylor Woodrow (Box 243)
    - Stena Sealink, Warner-Lambert (Warner Wellcome, Glaxo Wellcome) (Box 11)
    - Taylor Woodrow Construction (Box 243)
    - Unilever (Box 3)
    - Unilever (Box 7)
    - Unilever (Box 8)
    - Unilever (Box 8A)
    - Unilever (Box 20)
    - Unilever (Box 23)
    - Unilever (Box 61)
    - Unilever (Box 61A)
    - Unilever (Persil) (Box 72)
    - Unilever (Box 86)
    - Unilever (Box 92A)
    - Unilever (Box 95)
    - Unilever, Atwood research on soap powder in Ireland (Box 107A)
    - Unilever, Rowntree (Box 108)
    - Unilever (Box 113)
    - Unilever (Box 150)
    - Unilever (Box 153)
    - Unilever (Box 176A)
    - Unilever (Box 203)
    - Unilever--Julie Harvey-Samuel (Box 209)
    - Unilever (Box 220)
    - Unilever (Box 226)
    - Unilever (Box 232)
    - Unilever (Box 237)
    - Unilever (Box 289)
    - Unilever (Box 338)
    - Unilever (Box 338A)
    - Unilever (Box 351)
    - Unilever (Box 351A)
    - Unilever (including video) (Box 214)
    - Unilever worldwide--Lux & Timotei 1987-88 (Box 160)
    - Unilever, Lux and Timotei (Box 161)
    - Unilever (Persil), Crown Paint (Box 163)
    - Unilever (Persil) (Box 130)
    - Unilever (Persil) (Box 130A)
    - Unilever, E. Griffith Hughes, Goodyear, Hudson Knight (Box 279A)
    - Unilever (Box 41)
    - Unilever, Rowntree/Nestlé (Box 170)
    - Warner-Lambert, Unilever/Elida Gibbs (Box 178)
    - Warner-Lambert (Box 53)
    - Warner-Lambert (Box 62)
    - Warner-Lambert (Box 225)
    - Warner-Lambert (Box 275A)
    - Warner-Lambert (Box 345A)
    - Warner-Lambert (Benylin, Actifed, Listerine), BMRB mouthwash study (Box 27)
    - Wilkinson (Box 311)
  - Advertising Proofs and Proof Books
    - General (Box 62B)
    - General (Box 191)
    - General (Box 192)
    - General, Persil (Box 205)
    - General (Box 249)
    - General (Box 250)
    - General (Box 398)
    - General (Box 398A)
    - General (Box 398B)
    - General (Box 398C)
    - General (Box 398D)
    - General (Box 398E)
    - General (Box 355)
    - General (Box 356)
    - General, Kellogg's packaging (Box 231B)
    - General, old stuff--Guinness, Chesebrough-Pond's, Guardian, Ford (Box 279)
    - General, slides (Box 294)
    - General, slides (Box 294A)
    - Addis (Box 168)
    - Barclay's (Box 14)
    - Beecham Wines (Campari) 1962-75 (Box 10B)
    - Campbell's, Persil (Box 249)
    - ITV Association (Box 29A)
    - JWT house advertisements (Box 204)
    - Kensitas (Box 83)
    - Listerine advertisements, transit cards (Box 53)
    - Mackeson (Box 10)
    - Persil (Box 393)
    - Pond's (Box 10A)
    - Press ads (originally set aside for UEL students) (Box 244)
    - Press ads (Box 244A)
    - Proof books, 1931, Singer Motor (Box 125)
    - Proof books, 1931, Singer Motor (Box 125A)
    - Steel Company of Wales, Stock Exchange, Swakara, Taunton Cider, Taylor Woodrow Construction (Box 243A)
    - Steel Co. of Wales, Stock Exchange, Swakara, Taunton (Box 243B)
    - Vaseline 1926-1937 (Box 10)
    - Vaseline hair tonic 1933-1937 (Box 10A)
    - Vaseline scrapbooks, 1930s (Box 334)
    - Vaseline scrapbooks (Box 334A)
  - Books and Publications
    - Books (Box 159)
    - Books (Box 214A)
    - Books (Box 248)
    - Books (Box 259)
    - Books (Box 260)
    - Books (Box 264)
    - Books (Box 265)
    - Books (Box 268)
    - Books (Box 272)
    - Books (Box 275)
    - Books (Box 276)
    - Books (Box 297)
    - Books (Box 297A)
    - Books (Box 316)
    - Books (Box 316A)
    - Books (Box 323)
    - Books (Box 357)
    - Books (Box 357A)
    - Books (Box 364)
    - Books (Box 364A)
    - Books (Box 367)
    - Books (Box 367A)
    - Books (Box 372)
    - Books (Box 372A)
    - Books (Box 377)
    - Books (Box 377A)
    - Books (Box 389)
    - Books (Box 389A)
    - Books, bound reports (Box 221)
    - Publications
      - Admap (Box 382)
      - Admap (Box 387)
      - Admap; Mintel New Product Development News (Box 177)
      - Advertising Age (Box 126)
      - Advertising Age (Box 126A)
      - Advertising industry publications, 1980s-90s; Ad Age 1980s (Box 21)
      - British Design; Art Directors Annuals; miscellaneous books (Box 362)
      - British Design; Art Directors Annuals; miscellaneous books (Box 362A)
      - Broadcast media reports (Box 156A)
      - Broadcast media reports (BBC handbooks) (Box 162)
      - Campaign Magazine (Box 5)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 88)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 88A)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 90)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 90A)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 133)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 157)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 166A)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 270)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 270A)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 312)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 315)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 325)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 325A)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 353)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 353A)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 355)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 356)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 360)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 381)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 383)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 383A)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 386)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 391)
      - Campaign magazine (Box 391A)
      - Campaign magazine; Graphis Poster Annual (Box 368)
      - Consumer Affairs (Box 280)
      - Euro Barometer (public opinion journal) (Box 275)
      - International Marketing Data & Statistics; Consumer Europe; miscellaneous marketing reports (Box 365)
      - International Marketing Data & Statistics; Consumer Europe; miscellaneous marketing reports (Box 365A)
      - Journal of Marketing; Journal of Marketing Research; Journal of Consumer Research (Box 57)
      - Journal of Marketing Research Society (Box 134)
      - Journal of Marketing Research Society; International Journal of Advertising (Box 134A)
      - JWT Focus On: Charities, Kids (Box 298)
        [Restrictions on Access: JWT Focus On is closed to non-JWT researchers until 2016.]
      - JWT Focus On: Household, Case Studies (Box 298A)
      - JWT Focus On: Cars, Humor, Lifestyles, Luxury Goods (Box 304)
      - JWT Focus On: Cars, Humor, Lifestyles, Luxury Goods (Box 304A)
      - JWT Focus On: Media, Nestle (Box 307)
      - JWT Focus On: Royal Air Force (Box 307A)
      - JWT Focus On: Healthcare, Gambling/Lottery, Drinks (Box 327)
      - JWT Focus On: DeBeers (Box 327A)
      - JWT Focus On (Box 374)
      - JWT Focus On (Box 374A)
      - JWT Focus On, miscellaneous publications (Box 305)
      - JWT Information Centre newsletter (Box 275)
      - JWT publication, New Housewife (Box 392)
      - JWT Publications (Box 48)
      - JWT publications (Box 137)
      - JWT publications (Box 198)
      - JWT publications (Box 264)
      - JWT publications (Box 376)
      - JWT publications and newsletters (Box 390)
      - Knowledge Centre publications (Box 131)
      - Leisure Futures (Box 211)
      - Media International; Media & Marketing Europe; Media (Asia's Media & Marketing Weekly); miscellaneous single issues and publications (Box 233)
      - Mintel Market Intelligence (Box 275)
      - Mintel Market Intelligence (Box 276)
      - Mintel Market Intelligence (Box 292)
      - Mintel Reports (Box 35)
      - Mintel Reports (Box 35A)
      - Mintel Reports (Box 46)
      - Mintel Reports, Campaign, JWT Nuts (Box 138)
      - Mintel Reports, Food & Drink 1998 (Box 13)
      - Miscellaneous publications (Box 166)
      - Miscellaneous publications (Box 264)
      - Round the Square (Box 15)
      - Social Trends (newsletter) (Box 292)
  - Individuals' Papers
    - David Baker (See also J&B account files) (Box 207)
    - David Baker (See also J&B account files) (Box 207A)
    - David Baker (Box 229)
    - Miles Colbrook (Box 6)
    - Miles Colebrook, 1993 (Box 19)
    - Miles Colbrook (Box 19A)
    - Miles Colbrook (Box 86)
    - Miles Colbrook (Box 115)
    - Michael Cooper-Evans (Box 142)
    - Michael Cooper-Evans; ITV (Box 110)
    - Michael Cooper-Evans; Unilever (Box 223)
    - Jack Cronin (Box 39)
    - Jack Cronin (Box 46A)
    - Jack Cronin (Box 47)
    - Jack Cronin correspondence (Box 58)
    - Jack Cronin correspondence (Box 79)
    - Jack Cronin (Box 104)
    - Jack Cronin (Box 122)
    - Jack Cronin (Box 136)
    - Jack Cronin (Box 144)
    - Jack Cronin (Box 163)
    - Jack Cronin (Box 172)
    - Jack Cronin (Box 216)
    - Jack Cronin (Box 234)
    - Jack Cronin (Box 238)
    - Jack Cronin (Box 242)
    - Jack Cronin (Box 347)
    - Jack Cronin (Box 347A)
      [Restrictions on Access: Personnel-related files, closed for 40 years]
    - Jack Cronin; European operations 1980s (Box 105)
    - Jack Cronin, 1981-1983; Operations Committee, 1984 (Box 104)
    - Jack Cronin (slide presentation, video) (Box 4)
    - Ron De Pear 1997-1998 (see also Media Department) (Box 106)
    - Ron de Pear? JWT Europe files/reports (Box 165)
    - David Faulkner (Box 132)
    - David Faulkner (Box 181)
    - David Faulkner (Box 181A)
    - David Faulkner (Box 184)
    - Charles Friend; Europe FCS, different offices (Box 114)
    - Judie Lannon alphabetical files (mostly writings and speeches) (Box 277)
    - Judie Lannon (Box 277A)
    - Judie Lannon, ESOMAR conference (Box 92)
    - Harry McAuslan (Box 50)
    - Julie McCarthy (Box 300)
    - Anthony Rau (see also New Business records) (Box 59)
    - Anthony Rau (Box 71)
    - Anthony Rau, JWT Charities (Box 120)
    - Anthony Rau (Box 180)
    - Anthony Rau (Box 180A)
    - Anthony Rau (Box 295)
    - Anthony Rau (Box 340)